drserkanaygin.com 2017-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic

This Privacy Policy covers how Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic collects, uses, protects and shares your Personal information. Please read this notice to learn more about Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic Privacy Policy.

### Personal Information

For purposes of this Policy, Personal Information is any information or data about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, gender, age, occupation, address, phone number, email address, personal interests, medical or health concerns etc., which are not otherwise publicly available, received orally or collected by using offline forms or by or through the Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic website. We may also collect Personal Information from third parties such as your health provider or physician, upon your express written permission or authorization.

We do not collect, store or disclose information about children under the age of 18 without parental consent. If we receive information from a child under the age of 18, we will use that information only to inform the child that we require his parental consent.

### Securing Personal Information

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic has implemented reasonable precautions to ensure that your Personal Information is protected and retained in a secure fashion against any disclosure, loss, unauthorized access, misuse, alteration or destruction.

However, no security system is completely protected, therefore we cannot warrant the absolute security of our database, nor can we guarantee that the personal information you provided us will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us or by us over the Internet.

### Disclosure of Personal Information

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic will disclose your Personal Information only to those of its employees, contractors, health care providers that need to know your Personal Information in order to provide you with the service required. Some of those employees, contractors and health care providers may be located outside of your home country; by using Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic website, you consent to transfer such information to them.

Moreover, your Personal Information may be disclosed under the following circumstances:

When Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic is required to do so by Court orders, or legal process, or when it exercises its legal rights or defends itself against legal claims; and

In the event of a merger and/or acquisition of Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic by/with another entity. However, Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic will notify you by email prior to transferring your Personal Information to the other entity.

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic will not use or disclose your Personal Information for any reason, other than the above mentioned, without your written authorization. You may withdraw consent to the use or disclosure of your Personal Information, in writing, at any time, however we cannot take back any uses or disclosures of your Personal Information already made with your authorization.

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic will not rent or sell your Personal Information to anyone. However, Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic does not warrant that your Personal Information collected will not be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic disclaims any warranties or representations relating to the maintenance or non-disclosure of your Personal Information occurred by way of inadvertent disclosures which are beyond the control of or not due to the fault or negligence of Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic reserves the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. You are kindly requested to frequently check for any changes in this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in its Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute an approval of such change

### Links to other Websites

This Privacy Policy only applies to Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic website. It does not apply to links or entities that Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic does not own or control, such as the medical institutions, health centers or any other entity listed in this website. When you click a link found on this website, which directs you to another site not owned or under the control of Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic, you are deemed to be subject to the privacy and security policies of that site.

### Concerns

If you have any concerns about Dr. Serkan AYGIN Clinic privacy policy for the website, please send your comments/questions to [info@drserkanaygin.com](mailto:info@drserkanaygin.com)
